{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The XSLT processor copies the elements of the stylesheet until it finds a command in the format:", "opta": "SELECT ... FROM ... WHERE.", "optb": "{item, action}.", "optc": "{for-each select}.", "optd": "<HTML>...<\\HTML>.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What standard, protocol or language was generalized to become a standard protocol for sending messages of any type, using any protocol?", "opta": "SOAP", "optb": "SGML", "optc": "SQL", "optd": "ADO", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is not true about XML Schemas:", "opta": "They are used to define the content and structure of data.", "optb": "They define a set of symbols and the relationships of those symbols.", "optc": "They are themselves XML documents.", "optd": "They have their own syntax.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The most popular way to materialize XML documents is to use:", "opta": "DTD.", "optb": "XSLT.", "optc": "HTML.", "optd": "SOAP.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With XML:", "opta": "views are not limited to one multi-valued path only.", "optb": "documents can automatically be generated from database data only.", "optc": "database data can automatically be extracted from XML documents only.", "optd": "With XML, all of the above are true.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To eliminate definition duplication, XML Schemas define:", "opta": "an intersection table.", "optb": "global elements.", "optc": "a normalized definition table.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is not true about SOAP?", "opta": "SOAP originally meant Simple Object Access Protocol.", "optb": "SOAP was defined as an XML-based standard for providing remote procedure calls over the Internet.", "optc": "SOAP now is just a name, not an acronym", "optd": "SOAP was an early form of XML.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "XML Schemas consist of:", "opta": "properties and methods.", "optb": "elements and attributes.", "optc": "structure and data.", "optd": "tables and relationships.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The expression FOR XML RAW tells SQL Server to:", "opta": "place the values of the columns as attributes in the resulting XML document.", "optb": "place the values of the columns into elements rather than attributes.", "optc": "place some columns into elements and others into attributes.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ADO.NET provides the ability to create and process in-memory databases called:", "opta": "views.", "optb": "relations.", "optc": "tables.", "optd": "datasets.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An XML component that defines the structure of a document is known as a(n):", "opta": "DOCTYPE.", "optb": "DTD.", "optc": "#PCDATA.", "optd": "HTML Stylesheet.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HTML is an application of a more robust document markup language called:", "opta": "XHTML.", "optb": "XML.", "optc": "SGML.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "XSLT processors evaluate each statement in the context of the match that has been made. That is, XSLT processors are:", "opta": "context oriented.", "optb": "procedural oriented.", "optc": "object oriented.", "optd": "relational oriented.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The DTD begins with the word:", "opta": "#PCDATA.", "optb": "XML.", "optc": "DOCTYPE.", "optd": "HTTPS.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is not true about XML?", "opta": "Web page display is the most important application of XML.", "optb": "With XML, there is a clear separation between document structure, content and materialization.", "optc": "XML is more powerful than HTML.", "optd": "XML documents have two sections.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is not true about XSLT?", "opta": "XSLT is a declarative transformation language.", "optb": "XSLT uses a set of rules that govern how a document is to be materialized is created.", "optc": "XSLT uses a set of procedures that specify how a document is to be programmed.", "optd": "XSLT is used to transform the input document into another document.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the XML data instance conforms to the DTD, the document is said to be:", "opta": "type-invalid.", "optb": "type-valid.", "optc": "not-type-valid.", "optd": "an HTML document.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "XML is:", "opta": "a subset of SGML only.", "optb": "a hybrid of document processing and database processing only.", "optc": "a standardized yet customizable way to describe the content of documents only.", "optd": "XML is all of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The document that is used by XSLT to indicate how to transform the elements of the XML document to another format is a(n):", "opta": "HTML page.", "optb": "DOCTYPE procedure.", "optc": "stylesheet.", "optd": "stored procedure.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If an XML document does not have a DTD, then by definition it is:", "opta": "not-type-valid.", "optb": "type-valid.", "optc": "an HTML document.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}